inwya.com 2017-09-12

# INWYA. Information Where You Are

## Terms & Conditions

These are the terms and conditions for use of the web sites of InWYA sas. Contact details appear at the end of these Terms. Advertisers on the Site will need a separate contract with InWYA sas. Mail us at info@inwya.com if you wish to advertise on the Site. We encourage such approaches. 

### Use of Website on These Conditions

All use of the web site inwya.com (“the Site”) is on the terms and conditions below.   
If you do not agree to these conditions cease use of the Site immediately.   
You may print and keep a copy of these terms. They are a legal agreement between us and can only be modified with our consent. We reserve the right to change the terms at our discretion by changing them on the Site.   
Goods or services available for purchase on the Site, such as hotel bookings and shopping are provided by our partners and comprise a contract between the user and our partner, not InWYA sas. Although InWYA sas uses its reasonable endeavours to ensure reputable suppliers are used on the Site it accepts no liability arising from supplies by such partners. All such sales are on the terms and conditions of the partner and the user which may be accessed from the Site.   
The user is responsible for reviewing and accepting the terms and conditions of each partner before making a booking. Because the contract is made between the user and partner, any questions or complaints should be made to the partner direct. To cancel or amend a booking, you must contact the partner direct. 

### Accuracy of Information

InWYA sas (“we”) do our best to ensure all information on the Site is accurate.   
If you find any inaccurate information on the Site let us know and we will correct it, where we agree, as soon as practicable.   
You should independently verify any information before relying upon it.   
We make no representations that information is accurate and up to date or complete and accept no liability for any loss or damage caused by inaccurate information. This Site gives a large amount of data and there will inevitably be errors in it, particularly because dates and times of events change and cancellations occur. You are advised to check directly with the organisers of the event concerned before making any arrangements. 

### Our Liability

We provide information on this Site free of any access charge and on the basis of no liability for the information given. In no event shall we be liable to you for any direct or indirect or consequential loss, loss of profit, revenue or good will arising from your use of the Site or information on the Site.   
We are a distributor (and not a publisher) of content supplied by third parties and users of the Site. Any opinions, advice, statements, services, offers, or other information or content expressed or made available by third parties, including information providers, or users, are those of the authors or distributors and not of us. We do not necessarily endorse nor are we responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any opinion, advice or statement made on the Site. 

### Barring From the Site

We reserve the right to bar users from the Site on a permanent or temporary basis at our discretion. Any such user shall be notified and must not then attempt to use the Site under any other name or through any other user. 

### Legal Jurisdiction and Dispute Resolution

Italian law shall apply to these terms, notwithstanding the jurisdiction where you are based. You irrevocably agree that the courts of Italy shall have exclusive jurisdiction to settle any dispute which may arise out of, under, or in connection with these Terms and for those purposes irrevocably submit all disputes to the jurisdiction of the Italian courts. The place of performance shall be Italy. 

### General

Any formal legal notices should be sent to us at the address at the end of these Terms by email confirmed by post.   
Failure by us to enforce a right does not result in waiver of such right.   
You may not assign or transfer your rights under this agreement. 

InWYA sas contact details:   
InWYA   
Contact Office   
Viale Matteotti 53/A   
50052, Certaldo (FI)   
Italy 

Tel. +39 0571 1820661   
Fax. +39 0571 1979050 

VAT registration number: IT 05888480489 

For email enquiries send email to info@inwya.com 

### Policy

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement describes the online information practices which we InWYA sas (“we”, “our”) employ in relating to the information which you (“you”, “your”) provide when using the inwya.com geoportal platform (“Website”) offered and sponsored by a specific commercial activity, our customer, (“provider”). By accessing and using the Website you are accepting and agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Statement. 

### The Information We Collect

We collect personally identifiable information relating to you including name, e-mail address, link to your social network profile, url of your image on the social network, sex, language, the geoportal you’re connecting to in the following situations: 

### Information you provide accepting the connect procedure with your preferred social network:

When you connect your social account to InWYA on the Website for personal authentication; 

### The collected automatically using coockies:

Whenever you interact with the Website, we receive and store certain types of information using “cookies”. We describe how we use “cookies” below. 

### How We Normally Use Information About You

  * We will only use your Personal Information for the purpose(s) for which you provide it to us – including, for example, to:
  * login to a hotspot wireless;
  * forwarding your post to your social network;
  * communicate with you about orders, products, services and promotional offers,
  * prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Website; and
  * enable the provider to see who did connect to the his web platform.

We only share your Personal Information with the specific provider you connected to. 

### Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites

Our Website may contain links to other websites whose information practices may be different to ours. You should consult the privacy notices of those third party sites as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by them. 

### Security

We employ security measures to prevent unauthorized access to information that we collect online. 

Please note that email correspondence with us is in free format text and cannot be encrypted. Accordingly please do not send any sensitive information such as credit card details or passwords via email. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer’s hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the “lifetime” of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number. 

When you visit our Website we send you a cookie. Cookies may be used in the following ways: 

To enable the personalisation features on our Website (which give you the ability to recall recently viewed pages and see information which you have input on line). 

To compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our Website and to help us improve the structure of our Website. We cannot identify you personally in this way. 

### Disabling / Enabling Cookies

You can accept or decline “cookies” by modifying the setting in your browser. Please note that if you disable “cookies” you may not be able to use all the features of our Website. 

### Revision to this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Statement or any part of it from time to time. Please review the Privacy Statement periodically for changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Statement applies from time to time to all information that we have about you. 

### How Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement or how we use your Personal Information you may contact us by email at info@inwya.com. If at any time you decide that you no longer wish us to hold or use any of your Personal Information or wish to change the use to which your Personal Information can be put, please let us know by emailing us at info@inwya.com 

### Controller of Your Information

Information which you provide to us or we gather from the Website is controlled primarily by: 

### InWYA sas

VAT Registered in Italy: IT05888480489 

Registered office: Viale Matteotti 53/A, 50052 Certaldo (FI), Italy.
